Compiled from "RobotPlayer.java"
public class android.robot.motion.RobotPlayer {
  public android.robot.motion.RobotPlayer();
  protected void finalize();
  public int setListener(android.robot.motion.RobotPlayer$Listener);
  public int setDataSource(java.lang.String);
  public int setDataSource(java.lang.String, int, int);
  public int setDataSource(byte[], int, int);
  public int prepare();
  public int start();
  public int pause();
  public int resume();
  public int stop();
  public int getDuration();
  public int getPosition();
  public int setPosition(int);
  public int setEnable(int);
  public int isEnable();
  public int release();
}
