Compiled from "SpeechService.java"
public abstract class android.robot.speech.SpeechService extends android.app.Service {
  protected static final int EMOTION_IDLE;
  protected static final int EMOTION_LISTEN;
  protected static final int EMOTION_TALK;
  protected static final int EMOTION_THINK;
  public static final java.lang.String EXTRA_ENABLE;
  public static final java.lang.String EXTRA_OPERATE;
  public static final java.lang.String EXTRA_TEXT;
  public static final java.lang.String PREFER_NAME;
  public static final java.lang.String SERVICE_NAME;
  public static final java.lang.String SPEECH_LISTEN_ACTION;
  public static final java.lang.String SPEECH_SERVICE_ACTION;
  public static final java.lang.String SPEECH_SETTING_ACTION;
  public static final java.lang.String SPEECH_SPEAK_ACTION;
  public static final java.lang.String SPEECH_UNDERSTAND_ACTION;
  public static final java.lang.String SPEECH_WAKEUP_ACTION;
  protected android.os.Handler mHandler;
  public android.robot.speech.SpeechService();
  protected abstract void onCreateAsr(android.robot.speech.SpeechService$InitCallback, android.robot.speech.SpeechManager$AsrListener);
  protected abstract void onCreateAvw(android.robot.speech.SpeechService$InitCallback, android.robot.speech.SpeechManager$AvwListener);
  protected abstract void onCreateNlu(android.robot.speech.SpeechService$InitCallback, android.robot.speech.SpeechManager$NluListener);
  protected abstract void onCreateTts(android.robot.speech.SpeechService$InitCallback, android.robot.speech.SpeechManager$TtsListener);
  protected void onCreateSpeech();
  protected void onDestroyAsr();
  protected void onDestroyAvw();
  protected void onDestroyNlu();
  protected void onDestroyTts();
  protected void onDestroySpeech();
  public void onCreate();
  protected void setChatEnablePersist(boolean);
  protected boolean getChatEnablePersist();
  protected void setAsrEnablePersist(boolean);
  protected boolean getAsrEnablePersist();
  protected void setAvwEnablePersist(boolean);
  protected boolean getAvwEnablePersist();
  protected void setNluEnablePersist(boolean);
  protected boolean getNluEnablePersist();
  protected void setTtsEnablePersist(boolean);
  protected boolean getTtsEnablePersist();
  protected void setTtsPitchPersist(int);
  protected int getTtsPitchPersist();
  protected void setTtsSpeedPersist(int);
  protected int getTtsSpeedPersist();
  protected void setTtsVolumePersist(int);
  protected int getTtsVolumePersist();
  protected void setConversationModeValuePersist(int);
  protected int getConversationModeValuePersist();
  public void onDestroy();
  public final android.os.IBinder onBind(android.content.Intent);
  public boolean isWakeWordMode();
  public boolean isWakenup();
  protected boolean getChatEnable();
  protected boolean setChatEnable(boolean);
  protected abstract boolean getAsrEnable();
  protected abstract boolean setAsrEnable(boolean);
  protected abstract boolean startListening();
  protected abstract boolean isListening();
  protected abstract boolean stopListening();
  protected abstract boolean getAvwEnable();
  protected abstract boolean setAvwEnable(boolean);
  protected abstract boolean startWakening();
  protected abstract boolean isWakening();
  protected abstract boolean stopWakening();
  protected abstract boolean getTtsEnable();
  protected abstract boolean setTtsEnable(boolean);
  protected abstract java.util.List<android.robot.speech.TtsSpeaker> getSpeakerList(java.lang.String);
  protected abstract android.robot.speech.TtsSpeaker getTtsSpeaker(java.lang.String);
  protected abstract boolean setTtsSpeaker(android.robot.speech.TtsSpeaker, java.lang.String);
  protected abstract int getTtsPitch();
  protected abstract int setTtsPitch(int);
  protected abstract int getTtsSpeed();
  protected abstract int setTtsSpeed(int);
  protected abstract int getTtsVolume();
  protected abstract int setTtsVolume(int);
  protected abstract boolean isSpeaking();
  protected abstract boolean setAsrExpectedResults(java.util.List<java.lang.String>);
  protected abstract boolean setLanguage(java.lang.String);
  protected int startSpeaking(java.lang.String);
  protected int startSpeaking(java.lang.String, boolean);
  protected int startSpeaking(java.lang.String, boolean, boolean);
  protected int startSpeaking(java.lang.String, int, int, int);
  protected abstract int startSpeaking(java.lang.String, java.lang.String, int, int, int, boolean, boolean);
  protected abstract int forceStartSpeaking(java.lang.String, int, int, int, boolean, boolean);
  protected abstract boolean isSpeaking(int);
  protected abstract boolean stopSpeaking(int);
  protected int startSynthesize(java.lang.String, java.lang.String);
  protected abstract int startSynthesize(java.lang.String, int, int, int, java.lang.String);
  protected abstract boolean isSynthesizing(int);
  protected abstract boolean stopSynthesize(int);
  protected abstract boolean getNluEnable();
  protected abstract boolean setNluEnable(boolean);
  protected abstract boolean isUnderstanding();
  protected abstract int startUnderstanding(java.lang.String);
  protected abstract boolean isUnderstanding(int);
  protected abstract boolean stopUnderstanding(int);
  protected abstract void onStartEmoji(int);
  protected abstract void onStopEmoji();
  protected abstract void notifyAsrResult(java.lang.String);
  protected abstract void notifyTtsEnd();
  protected abstract boolean onChangeAsrEngine(java.lang.String);
  protected boolean onAiEvent(android.robot.speech.AiEvent);
  protected abstract java.lang.String[] getSupportedWakewords();
  protected abstract java.lang.String getCurWakeword();
  protected abstract boolean switchWakeword(java.lang.String);
  protected abstract boolean setWakewordSensitivity(java.lang.String, float);
  protected abstract float getWakewordSensitivity(java.lang.String);
  protected abstract java.util.List<android.robot.speech.ConversationMode> getConversationModeList();
  protected void onWakeUp(int);
  protected void startEmoji(int);
  protected void stopEmoji();
  public static boolean isMainThread();
  public static boolean isMainThreadHandler(android.os.Handler);
}
